Guide to the Bert Stimmel Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Bert Stimmel papers
1785-2005
1950-2005
YCAL MSS 733
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
20.43
(50 boxes)
The collection contains research material, writings, printed material, photographs and audiovisual material, including sound and video recordings, scrapbooks, and other personal papers documenting the life and professional career of American-born performer and artistic director Bert Stimmel. Stimmel spent the bulk of his professional life in the U.S., from the late 1950s to early 1970s, and in Lebanon, from 1972 onward, and the collection features material accumulated around his professional activities during this 50 year period.
Stimmel, Bert
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Paul Richard Lemma, 2006.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 44-46 (sound and video recordings) Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 47-49 (computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Bert Stimmel (1920-)
Bert Stimmel, born 16 December 1920, is an American performer, choreographer, and artistic director. After serving as a tail-gunner in World Word II and, after an honorable discharge from the U.S. Air Force in 1945, Stimmel studied dance and theater in New York, New Haven (where he earned an MFA from Yale in 1947), and London. Stimmel then performed in London theaters in the late 1940s and early 1950s before touring for a few years with the Bert Stimmel Modern Dance Company. Stimmel returned to the U.S. in the late 1950s and for the next 15 years he worked as a choreographer, director, and instructor in various places in New York State. From 1972 until 1999 Stimmel served as aristic director of the Caracalla Dance Company in Beirut, Lebanon.
Biographical information taken from material in collection.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains research material, writings, printed material, photographs and audiovisual material, and scrapbooks and personal papers documenting the life and professional career of American-born performer and artistic director Bert Stimmel. Stimmel spent the bulk of his professional life in the U.S., from the late 1950s to early 1970s, and then in Lebanon, from 1972 onward, and the collection features material accumulated around his professional activities during this 50 year period.
Arrangement
Organized into two groupings: January 2006 Acquisition and May 2006 Acquisition.
Actors -- United States; Dancers -- United States -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Electronic documents; Photographic prints; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Actors -- United States -- 20th Century; Dancers -- United States -- 20th Century; Stimmel, Bert
- January 2006 Acquisition, 1785-2005; 20.22; (49 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 44-46 (sound and video recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Boxes 47-49 (computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Scope and Contents
  The January 2006 Acquisition includes research material, writings, printed material, photographs and audiovisual material, and scrapbooks and personal papers documenting the life and professional career of American-born performer and artistic director Bert Stimmel.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 847.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Paul Richard Lemma.
  - Postcards, negatives, etc.
    - Caracalla, 1982-1988, undated; 2 (Box 1)
    - Photographs and postcards of Egypt, undated (Box 1)
    - Caracalla Dance Company reference, undated (Box 1)
    - Lecture, 1964-1999, undated (Box 1)
    - My photos of postcards and Spain, 1967, undated (Box 1)
    - References to projects, 1971-1999, undated; 3 (Box 1)
    - References to projects, 1976-1999 (Box 1)
    - Memories of my past, 1899-1977, undated (Box 1)
    - Unidentified, 1985-1990, undated (Box 1)
    - To Dublin With Love, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Antique postcards, undated (Box 1)
    - Sunday New York Times papers, 2002-2003, undated (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1963-1966, undated (Box 1)
    - Negatives, undated; 2 (Box 2)
  - Photographs, negatives, etc.
    - Fashion, undated (Box 2)
    - Me, 1978-1990, undated (Box 2)
    - James Patrick, U.S. income, 2000-2002 (Box 2)
    - Costume, 1978, undated (Box 2)
    - Unidentified, 1952-2005, undated; 3 (Box 2)
    - Caracalla film negatives and small prints, 1966-1981, undated (Box 2)
    - Pictures of Stimmel, 1979-2005, undated (Box 2)
    - My photos, 1955-2004, undated; 4 (Box 2)
    - State Department grants, 1961-1971, undated (Box 2)
    - My poems in Hollywood, 1960, undated (Box 3)
    - Family heritage, undated (Box 3)
    - Me with Caracalla, 1965-1966, undated (Box 3)
    - My operettes, 1961-1969, undated (Box 3)
    - References to projects, 1999-2001, undated; 4 (Box 3)
  - References and negatives
    - Caracalla film negatives & small print, 1972-1987, undated (Box 3)
    - Arab fashion and types of dress, 1975-1984, undated (Box 3)
    - Me: film negatives and prints of costumes, undated (Box 3)
    - My references, 1953-1999, undated; 2 (Box 3)
    - My references with Caracalla, Columbia, 1968-2001, undated (Box 3)
    - My teaching in Egypt, 1962-1964 (Box 3)
    - My teaching: Movement lecture, 1996, undated (Box 3)
    - Lima, Ohio references, undated (Box 3)
    - Fashion references, 1983-1999, undated (Box 4)
    - Costume, undated (Box 4)
    - Me: film negatives and prints of antique costumes, undated (Box 4)
    - Costume, undated (Box 4)
    - Arab dress, undated (Box 4)
    - Early travel to Middle East, undated; 2 (Box 4)
    - Arab customs and lands, undated (Box 4)
    - Arab culture, undated (Box 4)
  - References and research
    - Head dress introduction, undated (Box 4)
    - Rural headdress, undated; 2 (Box 4)
    - Devil, undated; 2 (Box 4)
    - Devil, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Devil duplicates, undated (Box 5)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 5)
    - Rulers North Africa, Morocco, undated (Box 5)
    - Women's dress, undated (Box 5)
    - Arab dress, undated (Box 5)
    - Tribal introduction, undated (Box 5)
    - Rural women, regional, undated (Box 5)
    - Rural women, basic "Galibyah," Egypt, undated (Box 5)
    - Unidentified, 1948-2002, undated; 4 (Box 5)
    - Negatives, 1973-1988 (Box 5)
    - Me: film, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Caracalla, 1986, undated (Box 5)
    - Re-writes, 1968-1999, undated (Box 6)
    - Yale, 1962, undated (Box 6)
    - Sally Miles; Joan White, 1974-1995, undated (Box 6)
    - England, 1963, undated (Box 6)
    - Stage movement, undated (Box 6)
    - My movement class, 1996, undated (Box 6)
    - Fashion, 1968, undated; 2 (Box 6)
    - Sally Miles, 1976, undated (Box 6)
    - Cards from friends, 1986, undated (Box 6)
    - Theater bibliography, undated (Box 6)
    - Egypt, 1969 (Box 6)
    - My personal notes, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Joan White, undated (Box 6)
    - Daryl Hanson, 1963-1975, undated (Box 6)
    - My lecture for Ohio, 1965, undated (Box 6)
    - Videos, undated (Box 6)
    - Caracalla tours, 1980s (Box 6)
    - Memories, undated (Box 7)
    - Caracalla, 1986-1996, undated (Box 7)
    - Beirut, undated; 3 (Box 7)
    - My lectures, 1969, undated; 2 (Box 7)
    - Reference, 1971-2000, undated (Box 7)
    - Joan White, 1968-1988, undated (Box 7)
    - Chris Columbus, undated (Box 7)
    - Xeroxes of drawings of Middle East life, undated (Box 7)
    - Theater, undated (Box 7)
    - Rural men, undated (Box 7)
    - Me: film, undated (Box 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Joan White, undated (Box 7)
    - Beirut, undated; 3 (Box 8)
    - Clothing [?], undated (Box 8)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 8)
    - My dancing with Caracalla, undated (Box 8)
    - Pamphlets and programs, 1974-1996, undated (Box 8)
    - Unidentified, 2002-2004, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Caracalla's Company Ballet, undated (Box 8)
    - Fashion, undated (Box 8)
    - Caracalla, 1983-1992, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - City man: intro, undated (Box 8)
    - Biography, undated (Box 8)
    - Caracalla, 1978, undated (Box 8)
    - Costume, undated (Box 9)
    - Chestnuts Anyone?, 1971; 4 (Box 9)
    - The Waterbabies, 1961, undated; 3 (Box 9)
    - In the Renaissance, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Christopher Columbus, undated (Box 9)
    - Columbia University, 1962-1972 (Box 9)
    - The Naughty 18th Century, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Joan White, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - Fashion, undated (Box 9)
    - Ceylon, Kiss Me Kate, 1970-1972, undated (Box 9)
    - Wish I Had A Nickel, 1967-1968, undated (Box 9)
    - Genevieve, 1985-1998, undated (Box 9)
    - You Gotta Be in Pitchers!, 1969; 2 (Box 9)
    - The Waterbabies, 1961-1975; 2 (Box 9)
    - Me: film Lebanon, undated (Box 9)
    - The Loves of George Sand, undated (Box 9)
    - My certificates, 1944-1971, undated (Box 10)
    - The Hurdy-Gurdy, 1961 February 18 (Box 10)
    - Christopher Columbus, 1961, undated; 3 (Box 10)
    - Genevieve Maxwell, 1985-1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Fashion, 1982, undated (Box 10)
  - Postcards, slides, etc.
    - Postcards, undated; 2 (Box 10)
    - Negatives, 1964, undated (Box 10)
    - Antique engravings, undated (Box 10)
    - Antique postcards, undated (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, 2004 (Box 10)
  - Research
    - Photos with Caracalla, undated (Box 10)
    - Dancing, undated (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, circa 1964-1983; 4 (Box 10)
    - Joan White, 1968-1985, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Egypt, 1963-1998, undated (Box 11)
    - Movement exercises, undated (Box 11)
    - Costume references, undated (Box 11)
    - Unidentified, 1911-1997, undated; 4 (Box 11)
    - Reference, 1983, undated (Box 11)
    - My obrettos, undated (Box 11)
    - Reference, undated (Box 11)
    - Me, 1996, undated (Box 11)
    - My writing, undated (Box 11)
    - Fashion, undated (Box 11)
    - Lebanon, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Scrapbook, 1976
    - Hunter College, NY, 1958 (Box 11)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 11)
    - The Kirov Ballet, United States tour, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Bert, undated (Box 12)
    - Women head-dress, undated (Box 12)
    - Stage and theatre, 1983-1996, undated (Box 12)
    - Photocopies, notes and miscellaneous, undated (Box 12)
    - Tribal rural head-dress, 1987, undated (Box 12)
    - Wish I Had a Nickel, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Passports, 1960s-1990s (Box 13)
    - Electronic files, undated; (130 computer disks) (Box 13)
      Computer disks are restricted. Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services.
      2006-ycal-0116-a-0001 - 2006-ycal-0116a-0130
  - Scrapbooks and Writings
    - Newspaper clippings and masquerade mask, 1949-1956, undated (Box 14)
    - Bert Stimmel, Egypt II, 1963-1964 (Box 15)
    - Photocopies of Bert Stimmel's Egypt II scrapbook contents, 1963-1964 (Box 16)
    - Brochures and newspaper clippings related to Caracalla, 1996, undated (Box 16)
    - Bert Stimmel, Ceylon, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Bert Stimmel, Lebanon, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Baalbeck Festival, 1965 (Box 19)
    - Baalbeck Festival, 1966 (Box 20)
    - Bert Stimmel, Egypt I, 1962-1963 (Box 21)
    - Untitled scrapbook, 1958-1961 (Box 22)
    - The Waterbabies, 1961 (Box 23)
    - Christopher Columbus, 1961 (Box 23)
    - George Loves Fred, 1968 (Box 23)
    - You Gotta Be in Pitchers, 1969 (Box 23)
    - Chestnuts Anyone?, 1971 (Box 23)
    - Bert Stimmel, London and Italy, 1948-1952 (Box 24)
    - Bert Stimmel Dance Company, 1953-1955 (Box 25)
  - Research
    - Bert Stimmel, 1983 (Box 26)
    - Untitled scrapbook, 1994 (Box 27)
    - Bert Stimmel, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Unbound scrapbook, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Bert Stimmel, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1961-1968; 3 (Box 31)
    - Untitled scrapbook, 1974 (Box 32)
    - Unbound scrapbook, 1970-1971; 2 (Box 33)
    - Unbound scrapbook, 1970-1971; 2 (Box 34)
    - Unbound scrapbook, 1966-1967; 3 (Box 35)
    - England / Scotland, 1976; 2 (Box 36)
    - Clippings, travels, etc., 1975 (Box 36)
    - My teaching at Columbia, 1990-1996 (Box 36)
    - Newspaper clippings, photographs, and ephemera, 1967-1968; 2 (Box 37)
    - Bert Stimmel, Afghanistan, Turkey, Iran, Greece, 1964 (Box 38)
    - To Dublin With Love, 1988 (Box 39)
    - Caracalla, 1980
  - Clippings of Images of North Africa and the Middle East
    - Illustrations and clipping from Baltou's Pictorial Drawing-Room Companion, undated (Box 40)
    - Illustrations from The Graphic, 1869-1897 (Box 40)
    - Clippings with illustrations from The Illustrated London News, 1850-1907 (Box 40)
    - The Illustrated London News (complete issues), 1882-1893 (Box 40)
    - Clippings and illustrations from The Illustrated Times, 1855-1868 (Box 40)
    - Illustration from L'Illustrazione Italia, undated (Box 40)
    - Clipping and illustration from Le Journal Illustre, undated (Box 40)
    - News From Afar: A Magazine For Young People (complete issues), 1903 January-April (Box 40)
    - Illustrations and clippings from Le Petit Journal, 1894-1904, undated (Box 40)
    - Illustrations from Le Petit Parisien, 1900-1905 (Box 40)
    - The Playgoer and Society Illustrated, 1911 (Box 40)
    - Risalat al-Jihad: Revue Culturelle et Islamique de l'Association de l'Appel Islamique, 1983 April (Box 40)
    - Clipping with illustration from Society, 1884 April 26 (Box 40)
    - Clipping with illustration from Le Tour du Monde, undated (Box 40)
  - Prints, Photographs and Postcards of People and Places in North Africa and the Middle East
    - Maps of Egypt and Syria, undated (Box 41)
    - Postcards (Arabic and English), undated (Box 41)
    - Photographs -- Artwork, undated (Box 41)
    - Photographs -- People, 1910-1983, undated (Box 41)
    - Print -- "Aladdin", undated (Box 41)
    - Prints -- Groups of people, 1785-1854, undated (Box 41)
    - Prints -- Individual people and costumes, 1804-1834, undated (Box 41)
    - Prints -- Landscapes and cityscapes, undated (Box 41)
    - Prints -- Military scenes, pirates and robbers, undated (Box 41)
    - Prints -- Miscellaneous, 1866, undated (Box 41)
  - Prints, Posters, Musical Scores, and Clippings of/inspired by North Africa and the Middle East
    - Posters -- Libyan Gehad Expedition, 1984 (Box 42)
    - Two prints grouped together by Stimmel, 1802-1811 (Box 42)
    - Print -- Ottoman Sultans and Turkish leaders (with commentary by Stimmel), 1984 (Box 42)
    - Prints -- Collected by Stimmel, "Ottoman Rulers", undated (Box 42)
    - Two clippings grouped together by Stimmel, 1858, undated (Box 42)
    - Life magazine articles about the Taj Mahal and Kathmandu, undated (Box 42)
    - Prints and articles grouped together by Stimmel (English and Arabic), 1953-1975, undated (Box 42)
    - Poster -- Folk Dance Festival (Beirut), undated (Box 42)
    - Pamphlet -- Egypt of Verdi, 1931 January (Box 42)
    - Illustrations and clippings grouped by Stimmel, undated (Box 42)
    - Playbill -- Mecca, 1920 (Box 42)
    - Two theater posters, 1817, undated (Box 42)
    - Miscellaneous prints, undated (Box 42)
    - Prints -- Middle Eastern people/scenes, undated; 2 (Box 42)
    - Musical compositions: Middle Eastern themed, undated (Box 42)
    - Musical compositions: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 42)
    - Pamphlet -- "Bella Donna", undated (Box 42)
    - Unbound scrapbooks, undated; 2 (Box 43)
    - Scrapbook, 1976 (Box 43)
    - Caracalla, 1980 (Box 43)
  - Audiovisual Materials
    Boxes 44-46 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Audiocassettes
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Untitled, undated; 1; 00:33:10; There is high background noise and hum on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398892)
      - Interview, Evelyn Howard, Beverly, MA, 1987 March 25; 1; 01:08:38; The program ends abruptly and is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398934)
      - "Biography / Dance Class", undated; 1; 01:09:14 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398942)
      - "Jacky Hovey translates French research for Bert" / "Encore", 1987 March 23; 1; 01:32:14; The program ends abruptly. Speed changes in the audio occur for about 30 seconds at about 01:01:30. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398959)
      - Research (1) / Biography (1), undated; 1; 01:30:14 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398967)
      - Untitled, undated; 1; 00:34:23; The program ends abruptly. The program is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398918)
        An orchestra is heard playing for approximately 34 minutes. The rest of the tape is of a radio program on the subject of writing.
      - "BBC - Meridian - Shakespeare Director", undated; 1; 00:43:47; The program begins abruptly. There are several breaks in content for the first 13 minutes of the audio. The program is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398900)
      - "Meridian", Stage Director Nicholas Heitner / "Meridian", Martha Graham, undated; 1; 01:56:28; There is a buzz on the tape. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398926)
      - Verdi's Nabooka, Lincoln Opera Center (1 of 3 cassettes), undated; 1; 00:49:38; There is a warble at the beginning of the audio and near the end at about 49:27. The program stops abruptly and restarts around 05:50. The program is in silence from about 48:28 until 49:13. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398868)
      - Untitled, Verdi's Nabooka, Lincoln Opera Center ? (2 of 3 cassettes), undated; 1; 00:41:42; The program begins and ends abruptly. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398876)
      - Untitled, Verdi's Nabooka, Lincoln Opera Center ? (3 of 3 cassettes), undated; 1; 00:32:56 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398884)
      - Jim Hatch interviews Bert, "Life in Lebanon" / Caracalla Dance / Lebanese Character, undated; 1; 01:02:41; The program is distorted at times. There is a high amount of hum and background noise on the tape. There is static as well. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398850)
      - Barbara Friend narration, excerpt from "Bird by Bird" by A. Lamott / Commercials, undated; 1; 00:08:25 (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398843)
      - Jim Hatch interviews Bert, "Life in Lebanon", undated; 1; 01:03:06; There is static on the tape. There is high background noise in the audio as well as a high amount of hum. The program is distorted at times. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398827)
        Content includes: life with Baalbeck Festival, life on the "events", and life inside Beirut.
      - Jim Hatch interviews Bert, "London Theatre Seat", undated; 1; 01:02:32; The program is distorted at times. There is a high amount of hum as well as background noise on the tape. (Box 44, Item barcode 39002091398835)
        Contents include: life before Europe.
      - Blank tape, undated (Box 44)
        This is an unwrapped, blank audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
      - empty case, "An American in Paris" by George Gershwin, undated (Box 44)
      - Fairuz. "The Days of Fakhr Eddeen" (1 of 2 cassettes), 1997; 1; 01:06:59; There is static on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002091398975)
      - Fairuz. "The Days of Fakhr Eddeen" (2 of 2 cassettes), 1997; 1; 01:09:39; The program is distorted at times. There is high frequency background noise on the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002091398983)
    - Compact disks
      - Sabah. "The Pinwheels", 1996 (Box 45)
      - Amália Rodrigues. "The Queen of the Fado", 1992 (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. "Black Tents", undated; (4 compact disks) (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. " Folklore", 1998; (3 compact disks) (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. "Andalusia the Lost Glory", 1998 (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. "Elissa, Queen of Carthage", 1998; (2 compact disks) (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. "Shot of Glory", undated (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. "Oriental Taming of the Shrew", undated; (2 compact disks) (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. "Oriental Night's Dream", undated; (3 compact disks) (Box 45)
      - Caracalla."Oriental Night's Dream" [Double CD], undated; (4 compact disks) (Box 45)
      - Caracalla. "Echoes", undated; (2 compact disks) (Box 45)
      - Fairuz. "The Days of Fakar Eddeer" [Double CD], 1991; (2 compact disks) (Box 45)
    - Video Recordings
      - "Caracalla in Malaysia", undated; YCALMSS733_0001; 1; 00:36:58 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002102369965)
      - "Caracalla in Malaysia", undated; YCALMSS733_0002; 1; 00:38:36 (Box 46, Item barcode 39002102369973)
  - Computer media
    - Computer disks, undated; (50 computer disks)
      2006-ycal-0116-a-0001 - 2006-ycal-0116-a-0050
      - SCENARIO NANFAX HATBOX ESCAPE, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0001; 1 (Box 47)
        Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - 4 FIGLEAF CAST TOUR -(B.B) WICKEDWO1 FIGLEAF INDEX INTROS2 HAKKAWAT DISCS IMPSOCIE GOLDTHRE SHOWS BITE2 USASHOWS SALLYMIL CASTOUR(B.B), 2006-ycal-0116-a-0002; 1 (Box 47)
      - 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0003 (Box 47)
      - ORBIT 1-2-3-4-5-6 SIMBEL 1-3-4-6-7-8-9 LIBAN 1-2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0004; 1 (Box 47)
      - 3 BITE 2 BITE 3 BITE 4, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0005; 1 (Box 47)
      - 4 BITE 2 SALLMIL ORBIT1 INTROS2 CASTOUR CASTOUR SHOWS INDEX DISCS USA SHOWS GOLDTHRE IMPSOCIE FIGLEAF1 HAKKAWAT WICKDWOL, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0006; 1 (Box 47)
      - 1 CRACKER 1 CRACKER 2 CRACKER 3 CRACKER 4 WIKWOR 1 WIKWOR 2 CRACKER 5 CRACKER BA WIKEDWOOD, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0007; 1 (Box 47)
      - 3 BUDDYS BUDDY5 RETURN UK PENNY.PLA PENNY 1 VARIETY THE BLACK OXFORD 2 DANCE LONDON FU SUNDOWN HEREXCEL TO DORSET SOLRTAL HEREXL2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0008; 1 (Box 47)
      - 4 MYDANCEC DANCECO2 DANCECO3 ITALY AT.V TELE SPAIN 1 CHESTER 1 CHESTER 2 CHESTER 3 JUBILEEG DANCEASC DEVIL.TIT ITALY2 PUSS BOOT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0009; 1 (Box 47)
      - 2 SS TIGER OLD VIC-1-2-3 LONDON 2 ST.DENIS TAKING AC TAKING AC 1 SUGAR SPI SUGAR SP 1 PARIS 1 RETURN US OXFORD WATERLOO LONDON 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0010; 1 (Box 47)
      - DEVIL'S PLAYGROUND 2 ORBIT 1-3-4-6 LI BAN 1-2 SIMBEL 1-3-4-6-7 8 SIMBLE 9-SEE DISC 3, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0011; 1 (Box 47)
      - 1 APPLE 1 APPLE 2 APPLE 3 SPHINX 1 SPHINX 2 SPHINX 3 BOSHARD 1 APPLE 9 NEW APP2 APPLE 90, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0012; 1 (Box 47)
      - REWRITES 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0013; 1 (Box 47)
      - A:\BERT (JIM'S) Recommendations Biblio.Leo *.bio, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0014; 1 (Box 47)
      - 3 TENTS 1-2-3-4-5-6-7-8-9-10-11, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0015; 1 (Box 47)
      - WICKED, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0016; 1 (Box 47)
      - TAPEORAN TAPERED, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0017; 1 (Box 47)
      - 1 APPLE-1-2-3 SPHINX-1-2 SHPHINX 3 BOSHARD 1 APPLE 9 NEW APP 2 APPLE 90, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0018; 1 (Box 47)
      - APPLES OF TEMPTATION SIMBEL 9 FLINTRO WESTINF1 16THCENT 17THCENT 19-20CEN, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0019; 1 (Box 47)
      - WICKED, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0020; 1 (Box 47)
      - ORBIT BITE2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0021; 1 (Box 47)
      - CAIRO 1 CAIRO 2 "BIZARRE"9, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0022; 1 (Box 47)
      - New "BACKSTAGE/BEIRUT", 2006-ycal-0116-a-0023; 1 (Box 47)
      - REWRITES 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0024; 1 (Box 47)
      - CRAKBA 1 CRACKER 4, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0025; 1 (Box 47)
      - 4 TRIC 2-3-4-5-6-7-8-9, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0026; 1 (Box 47)
      - SIMBEL, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0027; 1 (Box 47)
      - MILITARY:, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0028; 1 (Box 47)
      - BIG BEN 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0029; 1 (Box 47)
      - FOLKLORE DANCES (APPLE MAC), 2006-ycal-0116-a-0030; 1 (Box 47)
      - CRACKER, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0031; 1 (Box 47)
      - APPLE BITE 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0032; 1 (Box 47)